internet-turbo.com 2012-10-19

# Internet Turbo 2012

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Internet-Turbo.com website (the "Site"). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice (the "Policy") which applies to information provided or collected through this Site located at www.Internet-Turbo.com and in connection with Internet-Turbo.com's various services and software products (collectively, "Services").

Internet-Turbo.com and its affiliates, collectively "Internet-Turbo.com", are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains the data collection and usage practices of the Internet-Turbo.com website and products. We are providing you with this policy to inform you of the terms and conditions in reference to any information that is collected.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at [support@Internet-Turbo.com](mailto:support@Internet-Turbo.com)

Collection of personal information:

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way (for example, through surveys, questionnaires, information provided at registration and in the course of other communications with us). This includes identifiable information ("personal information").

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you, e.g. when subscribing to our e-mail newsletter, other opt-in communications, or when purchasing, downloading and/or registering Internet-Turbo.com products. The information we collect may include information that identifies you including your name, company or organization name, e-mail, phone, work or home address, and credit card information. When you visit our web site we gather certain general information about your visit, such as the IP address through which you access the Internet, the pages that you access while at the Site, the date and time you access the Site and the IP address of the web site which brought you to the Site. This information is used to help improve our services, analyze trends, and administer the Site.

The amount of personal and identifiable information you provide is up to you, and you are not obligated to provide such information. However, your use of the Site or the Services may be affected if such information is not provided.

You may provide information on behalf of another entity. If you completed the registration or provide information on behalf of a certain entity, you confirm that you were authorized by that entity at the time to give us consent to use the submitted information.

Collection of non-personal information:

When you open an HTML email message from us or install a third party application offered by us during installation of one of our products, we automatically record certain data using technology, including cookies and IP addresses. This data includes the email message you opened and the third party application you installed. This data helps us evaluate the effectiveness of our email and advertising campaigns. The stored Automatically Collected Information does not contain any information that can personally identify you or any of our users. We also track user traffic patterns from standard web server log files. We store statistics about domain names, browser types and IP addresses.

Use of personal information:

The personal information collected on our Site will be used to operate Internet-Turbo.com and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product(s) that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. When you sign up for our newsletter, we may use customized links or similar technologies to track e-mail links that you click. We may associate that information with your personal information in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or purchase information.

Information sharing and disclosure:

We will not sell, share, rent or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy. We may disclose your personal information to:

> ·       Third-party vendors who provide services to us or facilitate or evaluate the Sites or Services, such as shipping companies to fulfill orders, and credit card processing companies billing for goods and services, live chat providers assisting our clients with the checkout process or if they have questions or concerns regarding our products or services, e-mail service providers sending e-mails on our behalf, and third party vendors who host our shopping cart. Our merchant service provider's privacy policy governs the collection and use of the information collected within the shopping cart area of the Site; our service provider just hosts the platform and neither we nor our service provider have access to the information collected by the merchant service provider. We may also authorize third-party vendors or service providers to collect information on our behalf.

·       Business partners with whom we may jointly offer products or services, or whose products or services may be offered on our website or together with our software. You can tell when a third party is involved in a product or service because their name will appear, either alone or with ours. If you choose to use these products or services, we may share information about you, including your personal information, with those partners. Please note that we do not control the privacy practices of these third-party business partners. If you wish to no longer allow that third party to use your information you may opt-out by contacting that third party directly.

·       Referring websites. If you were referred to this website from another site (for example, through a link you clicked on another site that directed you to this one), we may share some information about you with that referring website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any website that referred you here.

·       Companies within our corporate family that are involved in operating or providing the Services. We may share your personal information with our affiliates. Our affiliates will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Policy, including requests that personal information not be used to provide you with Services.

We may share aggregated or anonymous data with third parties for any use whatsoever.

We also may share your information:

·       In response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process or in response to a law enforcement agency's request; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases we reserve the right to raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

·       When we believe it is appropriate to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company or this website, our customers, or others; and in connection with our Terms and Conditions for the Site, End User License Agreements for our Software and other agreements.

·       In the event that our business goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

Other than as set out above, you will be notified when personal information about you will be shared with third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share such information.

We do not sell, rent or lease the personal information that you provide about yourself to third parties unless we have your consent.

By providing personal information or using our Site or Services, you consent to the transfer of information outside your country in connection with the transfers of information described in this Privacy Policy, even to countries that might not offer a level of protection for your personal information that is equivalent to the one offered in your country of residence.

We also may share aggregate or anonymous information with third parties without restriction.

Use of cookies:

We may set and access cookies on your computer. Cookies are small text files that most web sites, including Internet-Turbo.com, place on your computer. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Most web browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can modify your browser setting to accept or decline cookies. Some of our web pages may require that you accept cookies. If you decide or set your browser not to accept cookies you will not be able to access those web pages. For information on how to disable cookies you should consult the instructions that accompanied your web browser.

Minors:

No information may be submitted to us via the Site by persons who are minors under their applicable local legislation. In the event you are a minor or younger than legal age in your country, you will need consent from your parent(s) or other legal guardian(s) before submitting any information to us via the Site, with the exception if such activities are allowed by applicable law of your country. We look forward hearing from you: [support@Internet-Turbo.com](mailto:support@Internet-Turbo.com)
